24小时
第三季  第22集
前情提要
我刚和一个安插在基勒竞选办公室的眼线通完电话
I just got off the phone with one of my sources over at Keeler's headquarters.
雪莉去那私下会见了基勒
Sherry was there meeting privately with Keeler.
见基勒干什么?
Meeting Keeler about what?
他打探不到 大卫
He didn't know. David.
我来这里是为了让你能在11月赢的大选
I came here because I can guarantee you a win in November.
大卫·帕默尔是谋杀案的同谋
David Palmer is an accessory to murder.
大卫昨晚向警察总长撒谎 为我提供不在场证明
David lied to the Chief of Police last night in order to provide an alibi for me.
你为什么要骗我?
Why are you lying to me?
我糗大了
I screwed up earlier.
传送到系统上的卫星录像 像是我们内部人伪造的
The SAT transmission on my system was forged by my own people.
犯错是一回事
Making a mistake is one thing.
企图掩盖错误是另一回事
Covering it up is another.
你不能再待在这了
I can't let you stay in place.
现在我来接管反恐局
I am taking over command of CTU now.
我是犯了个错误 杰克
I made a mistake,Jack.
不 托尼
No,Tony.
你犯下两个错误
You made two.
我会让你和你丈夫通话
I am going to let you speak to your husband.
告诉他你很好 平安无事
Tell him that you are ok and you are being treated well.
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
我还好
I am fine.
别听他们的 别?
Don't let them do this,don't let??
如果到时候你还没放简 等着收尸吧
If Jane is not release when I order it,your wife dies.
给我记住了
That's all you need to know.
明白了吗?
Are we clear?
从现在开始 由我暂管反恐局
From this point on,I am assuming control of CTU.
托尼·阿尔梅达引退辞职
Tony Almeida has stepped down.
我要押送简 桑德斯去分局
I'm taking Jane Saunders to Division.
这是移交手续
Here's the order.
-我们离开这里  -好
-We are leaving right now.  -Ok.
这边走
Going out this way right here.
警卫都去哪儿了?
Where are all the guards?
我们不需要警卫
We don't need those guards anymore.
杰克 托尼把我锁在这
Jack,Tony locked me in here.
桑德斯抓走了米歇尔来换取他女儿
Saunders has Michelle,he's using her as leverage to get his daughter out.
我是阿尔梅达 我把她救出来了 现在在我边上
This is Almeida. We are out. I have got her.
20分钟后再给你新的指令
I will give you further instructions in 20 minutes.
各出口注意 截住托尼·阿尔梅达
Exit security,I need a 20 on Tony Almeida.
以下事件发生于10点至11点之间
The following takes place between 10:00 am and 11:00 am.
让让
Excuse me.
克萝伊 调出大楼所有出口的监控录像
Chloe,I want you to pull up all the surveillance tape from every exit in this building.
重点看最后十分钟
I want you to focus on the last 10 minutes.
亚当 连上交通监控系统了吗?
Adam,have you linked up with traffic surveillance yet?
正在优先接入
I'm working on top chance.
杰克 我刚听说托尼私自带走了简 桑德斯
Jack,I just heard Tony took Jane Saunders out of the building without authorization.
-没错  -怎么回事?
-That's right.  -Why?
桑德斯抓了米歇尔
Saunders has Michelle.
想用她来换回女儿
He wants to trade her for his daughter.
简 桑德斯是我们唯一的筹码
Jane Saunders is the only leverage we have.
行了 蔡斯 我知道
Trust me,Chase. I know that.
有发现 他三分钟前离开这 90秒后驶出大楼
I got him. He left the building 3 minutes ago,and drove off the premises 90 seconds later.
亚当 是辆银色的SUV
Adam,he's in a silver SUV.
蔡斯 让行动组随时待命
Chase,I want you to prep the tactical team.
-收到命令立刻行动  -没问题
-Be ready to move as soon as I give you an order.  -All right.
找到他了杰克
I got him,Jack.
他在第五大街 离这儿半英里 正向东行驶
He's on 5th about half a mile from here,heading east.
我上车后再联络你
I will call you from the car.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
你没事吧?
Are you ok?
堵车了
It's just traffic.
我们离开后你表现得很奇怪
You have been acting all wired since we left.
没错 有很多事将要发生
Yeah,well,there's a lot going on right now.
你还没说为什么要把我押送到分局去
You never really explained why you wanted to transfer me to this division place.
我早就说了
I told you.
我知道你说了什么 但我难以理解
I know what you told me. It doesn't make sense.
听着 我现在没工夫和你解释
Yeah,well,I don't have the time to explain it to you right now.
阿尔梅达已经救出我女儿了
Almeida got my daughter out of CTU.
你随时待命
You need to be ready to move the moment I tell you.
何时给阿尔梅达下达指令?
When are you calling Almeida with instructions?
15分钟后 我会和弗莱德里克在一起
15 minutes. I will be with Fredrick.
酒店那至少有800人正面临生命威胁
At least 800 people are dead or dying in the Chandler Plaza Hotel.
就因为桑德斯在通风系统里 释放了生化病毒
because Saunders released a weaponized virus into the ventilation system.
媒体上的报道都是假的
What the media is reporting is a cover story.
他们掩盖真相是怕引起大面积的恐慌
They are deflecting the truth to avoid mass panic.
你会和其他人一样感染病毒
You will be infected along with everyone else.
不管多少钱 都不值得让你搭上性命
No matter what he's paying you,it's not worth losing your life.
杰克正在追踪托尼 一旦发现桑德斯的所在立马出发 明白吗?
Jack is in pursuit of Tony. Move out as soon as we get a location on Saunders. Understand?
很好
Good.
-金  -啊
-Kim.  -Yeah.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
正在和其他人监视我父亲
I am working with a team that's monitoring my father.
你想你正在安排行动小组
I thought you were setting up a tactical unit.
是的
Yeah,I am.
我们在等他们发现桑德斯的藏匿处
We have to wait until we get a location on Saunders.
我们随时准备出发
Until then,we are pretty much on standby.
-好的  -听着
-All right.  -Listen.
在我出去之前 我想和你谈谈
Before I have to go back out there,I want to talk to you.
谈什么?
About what?
我们之间的事
About us.
我要知道我们之间到底是什么关系
I need to know whether there's going to be an us.
听着 我也想了很多 但...
Look,I have been thinking about it a lot,and...
但那孩子改变了一切
the baby changes everything.
没有改变我对你的感觉
It doesn't change the way I feel about you.
先别管我
Look,let's forget about me for a second.
你的女儿 你的工作都不可能让我们在一起
You have a daughter and a job that won't let you be with her.
这是你的想法 还是你父亲的?
Is that you talking,or your father?
我父亲的话 早就会承认
My dad would be the first one to admit it.
他不是个好父亲
He wasn't the greatest dad.
并不是因为他不爱我
And it wasn't because he didn't love me.
我知道他很爱我
I know he loved me.
可是他做的是这种工作
It was because of his job.
如果我不再做外勤人员 你愿意和我在一起吗?
If I transferred out of Field Ops,would you consider staying with me?
我愿意
I want to stay with you,
我愿意和你一起养大孩子 蔡斯
and I would raise a child with you,Chase.
但不会为了你养大孩子
I just won't raise one for you.
亚当 他还在第五大街上吗?
Adam,is he still on 5th street?
不 我跟丢了
No,I lost him.
肯定在贾维斯街和希尔街之间转弯了
He must have turned between Jarvis and Hill.
扩大搜索范围
Widen the search.
正在进行
I am.
杰克 找到他了
Ok,Jack,I have got him.
他正在瓦因街向南行驶 希尔街下面两个街区
He's going south on Vine,2 blocks below Hill
-你可以从...  -行了 我知道
-You can save some time by...  -Ok,I got it
他遇上塞车了
He's hit traffic at Fillmore.
你也许能在格朗大街截住他
You might be able to intercept on Grant.
我知道你在撒谎
Look,I know you are lying to me
我知道你不是押送我去分局
I know you are not taking me to division.
你会没事的 简 好吗?
You will be fine,Jane. All right?
那至少告诉我现在要到哪去
At least tell me where we are going.
你要带我去哪?
Where are you taking me?
将你交还给你父亲
Back to your father.
我爸爸?
My father?
为什么?
Why?
他抓了我妻子做人质
He's holding my wife hostage,
如果我不把你送回去 他会杀我妻子
and he will kill her if I don't take you back to him.
这么说 你是在绑架我
So,basically,you are kidnapping me.
抱歉
I am sorry.
你见过他做的事知道 还信他的话阿?
After everything he's done,how can you be sure he'll do what he says?
也许他照样会杀了你妻子?
How do you know he won't kill your wife,anyway?
我没别的路可走
I don't have a choice.
我也希望有的选择 但是没有
I wish I did,but I don't.
托尼 把枪放到仪表盘上
Tony,put that gun on the dash.
把枪放到仪表盘上 快!
Put that gun on the dash,now!
慢慢下车
Slowly get out of the car.
简
Jane,
待着别动 会没事的
stay where you are,everything is going to be fine.
桑德斯抓了米歇尔
Saunders has Michelle.
我知道
I know.
他想用米歇尔换回他女儿
He wants to make a trade,Michelle for his daughter.
我知道 但这不行
I know. I can't let that happen.
听着 我今天已经差点失去她了 杰克
Look,I almost lost her once today,Jack.
我不会再让她受到任何伤害
I am not losing her again.
托尼 听我说
Tony,listen to me.
我很明白你的感受 我也曾经历过
I understand exactly how you are feeling. I have been there.
你就是像我这样处理的 将所有事抛诸脑后
And you handled it just like me,you kept everyone outside of it.
托尼 现在情况不一样
Tony,this is different.
几百万人正命悬一线
Millions of lives are at stake.
哦 这规则适用其他人
Oh,rules apply to other people.
但不适用于你 对吗 杰克?
But not to you,right,Jack?
托尼 拜托你冷静下来 好吗? 拜托
Tony,just calm down,ok? Come on.
你让我完成交换 我就去自首
You help me make this trade,I will turn myself in.
进监狱或者是怎么样我都不在乎
Go to prison,whatever is gotta happen.
我不能这么做
I can't do it.
我们需要用简来诱捕她父亲
We need Jane to lure her father in.
难道要米歇尔赔上性命?
Even if it means Michelle's gotta die.
米歇尔不会死的
Michelle doesn't have to die.
我们可以骗倒桑德斯
We can string Saunders along.
我需要你的帮助
I need you to start working with me
蔡斯 已经组织了特别行动小组
Chase has already got a strike team mobile.
不 不 不 不
No,no,no,no.
桑德斯一旦看到反恐小组 他会杀了米歇尔
Saunders sees I brought CTU into this,he kills Michelle.
他不会知道
He's not going to know we are there.
托尼 你们约在哪见面?
Tony,where are you meeting him?
托尼 你没的选择
Tony,you don't have a choice right now.
我们现在同坐一条船
You've got to work with me on this.
见面地点在哪?
Where is the meeting?
快说 你们约在哪见面?
Come on,where are you meeting him?
他让我五分钟后到泰勒街和瓦因街交叉口的公用电话亭
He wants me to be at a public pay phone at the corner of Taylor and Vine in 5 minutes.
然后再给我下一步指示
He'll give me further instructions from there.
谢谢
Thank you.
你做了正确的选择
You are doing the right thing.
隔离区用红色圆圈标记
The quarantined areas are circled in red.
目前我们已经控制住病毒扩散
Now,as far as we know,we have containment.
还不能确定?
We are still not certain?
是的 无法确定在几时
No. But we can't really be certain for hours.
或几天之内
Maybe days.
大卫 听好
David,listen.
外界给格里很大的压力
The press is breathing down Gerry's neck pretty hard.
他认为我们该发表一个声明
Now,he thinks we should release a statement.
我已经发表过了
I already have.
我已经关闭了公交系统 并让人们不要外出
I have closed down public transportation and I have told the people to stay in their homes.
还派出F18战斗机在空中巡逻
We have F18s patrolling the skies.
但我们并没提及到底是什么威胁 而外界开始流言四起了
Yeah,but we haven't revealed the exact nature of this threat and the press is picking up on that.
4000平方英里的地方住了1000多万人
We have 10 million people spread out over 4000 square mile area.
即使是其中一小部分人 同时决定逃离
If even a small percentage decide to leave at the same time,
都会引起无法控制的恐慌
it will ignite a public panic beyond anything we could control.
目前正确的选择是在控制病毒以前 守住这个秘密
The right thing to do is to withhold the truth until we are sure the virus is contained.
我会让格里尽量拖住媒体
I will tell Gerry to hold off on the press as long as he can.
总统先生
Mr. President.
怎么 珍妮
Yes,Jeannie.
基勒参议员要见您
Senator Keeler's here to see you.
请他进来
Have him brought in.
好的 先生
Yes sir.
你好 约翰
Hello,John.
总统先生
Mr. President.
请坐
Please take a seat.
谢谢 站着也一样
Thank you. I will stand.
听说你要见我 真是让我感到惊讶
You can imaging my surprise when I was told that you wanted to see me.
你打算主动放弃大选了吗?
Are you withdrawing from the race?
总统先生
Mr. President,
关于艾伦·米利肯的死
with respect to the death of Alan Milliken,
我知道你给了警方假口供
I know you lied to the police.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
你妨碍了对一起严重罪案的调查
You obstructed the investigation of a capital crime.
你这是诬蔑 约翰
That's a baseless charge,John.
我想你可能轻率了点
Though I have come to expect this kind of recklessness from you.
不 先生 这并非无赖 也非轻率
No,sir,it's neither baseless nor reckless.
这是一张硝化甘油瓶的照片 这原本能救他一命
This is a photograph of the nitroglycerine medicine that would have saved Milliken's life.
如果不是有人阻止的话
If it hadn't been kept from him.
你和警察说雪莉在米利肯死的时候和你在一起
You told the police Sherry was with you at the time of Milliken's death.
但她留在瓶子上的指纹能证明你在撒谎
Her fingerprints on this prescription bottle prove otherwise.
现在...
Now...
这个国家唯一能做的就是指控他们的总统...
the last thing this country needs is to have its President...
是一起谋杀案的同谋
dragged through the mud for complicity in a murder.
为什么把这个给我看 约翰?
Why are you showing me this,John?
你想怎么样?
What do you want?
希望你能主动下台
Your resignation.
当然不是现在
Not immediately,of course.
但这案子一了结
But once this crisis you are dealing with is over,
你可以用任何体面的理由辞职
you can resign with whatever face saving reason you want to give.
滚
Get out of here.
我是在给你一个保住面子的机会
I am offering you the chance to leave office with honor
免得你遗臭万年
to control how your legacy is written.
这买卖很合算 大卫
It's a good deal,David
你应该接受
You should take it.
他一分钟后就会来电话 我要去电话旁了
He's going to call in one minute. I should go to the phone.
当他告诉你交换地点的时
Ok,as soon as Saunders tells you where he wants he exchange to take place,
你要拒绝他
you need to reject the location.
我们须让他另选个地方 以便蔡斯有时间设下埋伏
We need to force him into picking a secondary location so Chase has time to embed his teams.
如果照他说的做 他会杀了米歇尔
If I don't show up where and when Saunders wants me to,he's going to kill Michelle.
只要他女儿在我们手上就不会
Not as long as we have his daughter.
如果他不同意呢?
What if he doesn't go for it?
不要给他选择的余地
Don't give him a choice.
尽量利用你手上的筹码 托尼
You have got some leverage here,Tony,use it.
好吧 我该走了
All right. I need to go.
我父亲因为我绑架了他妻子?
My father kidnapped his wife because of me?
没错
Something like that.
而你们现在想用我来诱捕他
And now you want to use me as bait to get to him.
我们会不惜一切阻止你父亲释放病毒
We are going to do whatever we have to to stop your father from releasing this virus.
待着别动 我们马上回来
Stay here. We'll be right back
交换地点在哪?
Where are we meeting?
先让我和我女儿说话
First,let me speak with my daughter.
不行 交换时有的是时间说话
No. You can talk to her when we make the exchange.
好吧
All right.
带她去你北边3英里远马尔汀路的一个工业园
Bring her to an industrial pack 3 miles north of where you are,on Maltin Road.
22号装载码头那里会有辆车等着
A car will be waiting at loading dock 22.
另选一个地方 那地方不行
Choose a new place. That doesn't work.
你看着办吧
Make it work.
10分钟内到达 否则等着给你妻子收尸吧
You have got 10 minutes to get to the industrial park or your wife will die.
如果在那儿见面 我们都会玩完
If we meet there,we all die.
真的吗?
Really?
反恐局有众多卫星监控那个区域
CTU has redundant satellite surveillance of that area.
他们在出动所有资源找我
They are dedicating all their resources to finding me right now.
如果想你女儿平安无事 换个新地点
If you want your daughter back safely,you pick a new spot.
我可不是在和你谈判 阿尔梅达先生
I am not negotiating terms,Mr. Almeida.
我等这一天很久了
I have planned too long and too hard for this day.
我将不惜一切确保计划顺利实施
and I will do whatever it takes to make sure nothing interferes.
即使...
Even...
即使要牺牲我女儿的性命
even if it means sacrificing my daughter.
你必须了解我的决心 阿尔梅达先生
You need to understand my commitment,Mr. Almeida
你他妈干什么? 他没有上当
What the hell are you doing? He wasn't going for it.
他在试探你
He is testing you. He's heard what you had to say.
他会再打来的 先挂了电话
He'll phone back. Now hang up the phone.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
因为他在想也许我会杀了他女儿
Because right now he thinks I am going to kill his daughter.
他必须确定他女儿还活着才会冒险露面
The only reason why he exposed himself is to make sure she's still safe.
这只是你的想法 杰克
Maybe that's what you'd do,Jack
但你可不是桑德斯
But you are not Saunders.
不管你有多了解他 你都不是他
No matter how well you think you know this guy,you are not him.
这不是场游戏 杰克
This isn't a game,Jack.
这关系到我妻子的性命
We are talking about my wife.
我们控制了交换地点 米歇尔生还的可能性更大
Michelle's got a better chance of surviving if we control the ground where the exchange is supposed to take place.
但救出她并不是你的首要任务 不是吗?
But protecting her is not your priority,is it?
如果她死了 这个结果也是可以接受的 不是吗?
If she were to get killed,that would be an acceptable loss,wouldn't it?
上帝啊 杰克
My god,Jack.
你忘了特里是怎么死的了吗?
Didn't you learn anything from what happened to Terry?
闭嘴 托尼
Shut up,Tony.
闭嘴
Shut up.
托尼
Tony
你为了工作牺牲你妻子 我可不会这么做
Just because you sacrificed your wife for this job doesn't mean I am going to sacrifice mine.
喂
I am here.
别再犯错误
Make no mistake.
给你唯一的机会
This is your first and your last accommodation.
告诉我交换地点
Just tell me where you want to make the exchange.
市区 第六大街桥下
Downtown,under the 6th street bridge.
第六大街桥下
Under the 6th street bridge.
30分钟内到达
Be there in 30 minutes.
如果我发现你带了其他人去
But if I see that you have brought anyone else into this,
等着收尸吧
I will kill your wife.
干得好
You did great
托尼·阿尔梅达要去交换人质了
Tony Almeida's going to make the exchange,
桑德斯出现之前
but until we get confirmation that Saunders is on site,
保持静默
we stay invisible.
我会在各路口布置关卡 走
I will assign positions on the way out. Let's go.
这是什么?
What is it?
第六大街桥的卫星图片
Satellite pictures of 6th street bridge.
我要的是实时画面 山姆
I asked for a real time feed,Sam
到了那就有了
We will have it,too,by the time we are on site.
空中支援怎么样?
What about air support?
已经联络海军配合我们行动
We are coordinating with the Marines.
他们随时待命
They will move on your order.
蔡斯 万事小心
Look,Chase,please be careful.
别担心 没事的
Don't worry about me. I will be fine.
克萝伊 要多久才建立第六大街桥的实时卫星图像连线?
Chloe,how much time before you can setup a real time satellite feed for the 6th street bridge?
你真以为蔡斯会为了家庭而不做外勤人员吗?
Do you really think Chase is going to quit field ops to start a family?
他才不会这么做
He won't.
我不知道你从哪听来的这些  但这不关你的事
I don't know where you are getting this from,but it's none of your business.
我认识蔡斯3年了
I have known Chase for 3 years.
你跟他在一起不过3个月
You have been dating him for 3 months.
你到底想说什么?
And your point being?
他也许是个好人 但他跟你父亲很像
He might be a great guy,but he's just like your father.
他们都是一类人
They are both the same person.
所以你想他放弃现在的工作是不可能的
So if you are expecting him to leave this for the suburbs,you should revise your expectations.
你要多久能建立卫星连接?
When can you uplink a satellite feed?
10分钟
10 minutes.
那就去做吧
Then do it.
我只是为了你好 金 仅此而已
I am just trying to be a friend,Kim. That's all.
喂
Hello.
你这次真是太过分了 雪莉
You have gone too far this time,Sherry.
我就知道你会打过来的 大卫
You know,I thought I might be hearing from you,David.
你让基勒来威胁我放弃总统的位置 ?
You sent Keeler over here to blackmail me into giving up my presidency?
哇 哇 哇 等等
Whoa,whoa,whoa,slow down.
你说基勒去找你?
You mean Keeler paid you a visit?
他干了什么你心里清楚
You know damn well he did and you know why.
只有你才有可能给他那个药瓶
Only one person could have given him that prescription bottle and that's you.
好吧 就算是
Ok,supposing that was true.
那又怎么样?
What then?
你会被扔进监狱
You should go to jail for murder.
你也会的 大卫
You should go to jail,too,David.
你对警方撒谎
You lied to the police.
你告诉他们我们一整晚都在一起
You told them that I was with you all night.
隐瞒证物 妨碍司法公正
Withholding evidence,obstruction of justice.
这些都是重罪
Those are serious crimes
我知道你一直想被载入史册 大卫
I knew you always wanted to go down in the history books,David.
但恐怕这样不行 没错吧?
But I am not certain like this. Am I right?
基勒给了你什么好处 雪莉?
What did Keeler offer you,Sherry?
正是你该给我的 尊重和地位
Exactly what you should have offered me,respect and a seat at the table,
但事实上你对我是呼之则来
but instead you called me up when you needed me.
喝之则去
and then after I did your little dirty work,You threw me out like an old pair of shoes.
你应该很了解我 雪莉
You know me,Sherry,
比任何人都了解我 你知道我不会受人威胁
better than anyone,and you know I won't be bullied.
在事情还没失去控制之前 你最好问问自己
So before this goes too far,you better ask yourself a question.
你愿意进监狱吗?
Are you willing to go to jail?
你知道吗 大卫 我已经问过自己很多次了
You know,David,I have asked myself that a million times
而答案就是 我愿意
and the answer is yes,I am willing to go to jail
问题是 你愿意吗?
The question is,are you?
我想你肯定不愿意
I didn't think so.
行动组分成两拨
I want the strike teams split into 2 groups.
A队埋伏在这里 B队埋伏在那边
Group A can take cover here,group B back here.
我们一到那 就马上部署好
I want them briefed and ready to go as soon as we get there.
如果桑德斯看到任何其他人 他是不会出现的
If Saunders sees anyone other than Tony or his daughter,he's not going to make the approach.
空中支援响应时间是多少?
What's the response time for air support?
30秒
30 seconds,after I give the order.
我会把坐标传给他们
I will relay the coordinates.
桥下见
I will see you at the bridge.
明白
You got it
我知道我父亲在酒店释放了病毒 害死了很多人
I know my father released the virus in the hotel that people died.
但你认为他会言出必行吗?
But do you really think he'll do what he's saying?
向全国释放病毒?
Release it all over the country?
如果我们不阻止他 他会
If we don't stop him,yes.
为什么?
Why?
他这么做肯定有原因的
There has to be a reason he's doing all of this.
当我和你父亲共事时 他一直致力于救死扶伤
When I worked with your father,he dedicated himself to saving the lives of innocent people.
他似乎受了什么打击
Something has happened to him.
我不清楚到底什么事
I don't know what.
但现在他认为是政府出卖了他
But now he believes our government's betrayed him.
是真的吗?
Is he right?
说不清楚
There's no easy answer to that.
你父亲从事工作需要他作出巨大的牺牲
The work that your father did often demanded that he make seemingly impossible sacrifices.
波斯尼亚发生的事显然超出了你父亲的承受范围
Whatever happened to your father in Bosnia was obviously a sacrifice he wasn't willing to make.
很抱歉
I am sorry.
不
No.
闭嘴! 没人能帮你
Shut up! No one can hear you.
不
No.
给我闭嘴
Shut up now.
不
No.
不! 上帝啊
No! Oh God.
我叫你停下 别再叫了
I said stop,stop screaming.
救救我 我被感染了
Look at me,I have been infected.
救我 救我 救我...
Help me,help me,help me...
不
No.
有麻烦了
We got a problem here.
出什么事了?
What's going on?
她染上了
She has it.
她感染了病毒
She has the virus.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
她在流血 肯定是在宾馆染上的
She's bleeding,she must have caught it at the hotel.
没经过测试 她不会被放出来
They wouldn't have release her without testing her.
你被耍了
It's a trick.
肯定是她自己弄出来的
She did it to herself.
凯文 你在吗?
Kevin,are you there?
凯文
Kevin.
快 守住东边走廊
All right,take the east corridor.
不能让她逃出去
Stop her from getting aboveground.
但不要杀了她
But do not shoot to kill.
反恐局 奥布莱恩
CTU,O'Brian.
我是米歇尔
It's Michelle.
喂?
Hello?
克萝伊 能听见吗?
Chloe,can you here me?
不管你是谁 我这边信号很差
Whoever this is,I have a really a bad connection.
我现在很忙 先挂了
I have got a lot of stuff to do right now.
克萝伊
Chloe.
基勒想怎么样?
So what did Keeler want?
他想坐我的位子
My job.
他有证据证明雪莉在艾伦·米利肯死的那晚在他家
He has proof that Sherry was at Alan Milliken's tonight.
什么?
What?
什么? 什么证据?
What,what proof?
艾伦·米利肯的药瓶上发现了雪莉的指纹
Alan Milliken's prescription bottle turned up with Sherry's fingerprints on it.
他怎么搞到这个的?
How did he get a hold of this?
你说呢?
How do you think?
是雪莉
Sherry.
我几分钟前刚和她通完电话
I talked to her a few minutes ago.
她直接就承认了
She didn't even bother to deny it.
大卫 她肯定是骗你的
David,she's got to be bluffing.
如果这个泄露出去 她是要坐牢的
I mean,if this gets out,she goes to jail.
我也会的
So will I.
她认为我会摔得更惨
She figures I have more to lose than she does.
她说的没错
And she's right.
基勒要你怎么做?
What does Keeler want you to do?
随便找个理由放弃大选
Withdraw from the race for whatever reason I choose.
党内会陷入混乱
The party gets thrown into chaos,
不论谁接替我的位置 都不可能赢得大选
whoever takes my place won't have a prayer in the election,
那么基勒就将当选总统
and Keeler becomes President.
天啊
Oh,my god.
一切都是我的错
This is all my fault.
嘿 听着
Hey,look
我们都错了
We both made mistakes.
是我叫雪莉来的
I am the one who called Sherry.
也许还有办法
There may be a way out of this.
什么办法
How.
除了这个是 雪莉手上就没别的证据了吧?
Without this,Sherry's got nothing,right?
你是说?
What are you suggesting?
那我们就让她失去唯一的筹码
That we take away the only leverage she has.
你的意思是 把证物偷走
You mean,steal evidence.
天啊 韦恩
My god,Wayne.
在你否决以前 考虑一下 好吗?
Before you say no,you just think about this,ok?
我可以叫福克斯顿让所有这一切都消失
Now,I can call Foxton,and he can make this all disappear.
你只需要点头就行了
All you have to do is give me the ok.
-看着她  -遵命
-Stay with her.  -Yes,sir.
突击队准备好了吗?
Is your strike team in place?
2分钟后一切就绪
2 minutes,they will be ready.
你能保证他们都隐藏好了?
You sure they will be of sight?
保证不会暴露的 托尼
They will be invisible,Tony.
好
Ok.
我去桥下掩护托尼
I am gonna back Tony up here at the 6th street bridge.
各就各位
We should get in position now.
金的急电
Jack,priority call from Kim.
我是杰克
This is Jack.
爸 我接到米歇尔的电话
Dad,I got Michelle on the line.
她还在桑德斯手里吗
Is she with Saunders
不 她已经逃出来了
No,she said she get away from him.
接过来
Patch her through.
等等
Hold on.
米歇尔 说吧
Michelle,go ahead.
我从桑德斯手中逃脱了 但他在追我
I got away from Saunders,but he's still after me.
米歇尔 是我 你在哪?
Michelle,it's me. Where are you?
威尔希尔·奥利弗东面的一个街区
Wilshire,a block east of Olive.
蔡斯 快派出你的突击队
Chase,send your strike team in now.
蔡斯 等等
Chase,don't.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
米歇尔 仔细听我说
Michelle,I want you to listen to me very carefully.
我要你回到桑德斯那里
I want you to let Saunders catch you again.
什么 你疯了吗?
What,are you crazy?
我们必须让交换按原计划进行
We have to let the exchange go down.
只有这样我们才能抓到他
It's the only way we are gonna catch him.
你要我自投罗网?
You want me to give myself up?
没错 交换地点已经被布控 他一出现我们就会派人行动
Yes,the exchange site is secure,I will send our people in as soon as we know he's there.
-蔡斯 叫你的人快去 这是命令  -蔡斯 等等!
-Chase,redirect your people now.That's an order.  -Chase,don't!.
杰克 你滚开
Jack,stay out of this.
你不是这的指挥官
You are not in command here.
马上把他带走
Get him out of here,now.
杰克 杰克 那是我妻子 杰克
Jack,Jack,that's my wife,Jack.
你这个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
那是我妻子
It's my wife.
杰克
Jack.
我们要照原计划进行
We need this exchange to go through.
成败在此一举 你明白吗?
Everything depends on it,do you understand me?
米歇尔 如果没有这次交换 我们就会失去抓他的机会
Michelle,if he doesn't have you for trade,he won't go through with the meeting.
听着 我们没有别的机会了
Look,we are not going to get another chance at it.
你明白吗 米歇尔
Do you understand,Michelle.
好吧
Yes.
我们会尽全力确保你的安全
We are gonna do everything we have to to make sure you come out of this ok.
但我们要马上行动
But we have got to move now.
各小组就位
Let's get our teams into position.
我原以为你大哥是个不会与我们为伍的政治家
And I thought your brother was the kind of politician who would never lower himself to my level.
我必须帮他扫清一切障碍
I need to recover something that could cause him a great deal of trouble.
什么东西?
What is it?
从犯罪现场被带走的一个药瓶
A bottle of medicine was taken from a crime scene.
有没有被呈为证据?
Has it been admitted into evidence?
没有
No.
是总统前妻雪莉 帕默尔的私人物品
It's in the possession of Sherry Palmer,the President's ex-wife.
我知道她在哪 也知道她在哪偷的
I have a pretty good idea where she is right now,and I can partially reconstruct where she's been since she stole it.
给我们多久?
What kind of time frame are we looking at?
小时 福克斯顿 不是天
Hours,Foxton,not days.
这项行动是总统的意思吗?
Has this operation been authorized by the President?
有什么区别吗?
What difference does it make?
报酬不会少的
You will get your money.
我不是担心这个 我只是想知道在为谁做事
I am not worried about that,I just need to know who I am working for.
我哥知道你们是干什么的
My brother knows what you are doing.
不是我不信任你 只不过...
Not that I don't trust you,but ...
我要亲自得到他的委托
I'd like to hear it from him.
好
Fine.
这样可以了吗
That's proof enough.
出发
Let's go.
蔡斯和他的人发现桑德斯了吗?
Chase and his men have Saunders yet?
还没
No one's coming yet.
听着 杰克
Look,Jack,
向我保证你不会在确保米歇尔安全之前对桑德斯动手
promise me you won't make a move on Saunders until Michelle is safe.
我们一见到桑德斯就会行动 托尼
We are going to move as soon as we have got a visual on Saunders,Tony.
我们必须这么做
That's the way it's got to go.
我明白
I know.
我只希望你能尽全力
I am just asking you to do what you can.
我会的
You know I will.
有3辆车从西面驶来
We have got 3 cars headed in from the west.
托尼 他们来了 你准备好了吗?
Tony,they are coming. Are you ready?
是的
Yeah.
车窗有防护膜 我看不见里面的情况
The windows are tinted. I can't see inside.
喂
Yeah.
让她听电话
Give her the phone.
我希望能毫发无损的将你交还给你丈夫
My preference is to turn you over to your husband unharmed
但万一出了什么差池 我就会杀了你
But I will kill you if anything goes wrong.
喂
Yeah.
我见到我女儿 就会马上放了你妻子
When I see my daughter,you will get your wife.
没问题
All right.
简 下车
Jane,I need you to get out of the car.
好了 没事的
Ok,everything is going to be ok.
走去你父亲那
I want you to walk over to your father's men.
我父亲在哪?
Where's my father?
我不知道
We don't know.
听着 必须这么做 简
Listen,we have to do this,Jane.
抱歉
I am sorry.
听着 简 你一定要相信我
Look,Jane,you have got to trust me on this.
快去吧 求你了
Please go. Come on.
杰克 可以行动了
Jack,send your men in now.
我们没见到桑德斯本人 重复 还没见到桑德斯本人
We don't have a visual on Saunders. I repeat we don't have a visual on Saunders.
我不要
I can't.
-嘿 过来  -简 别回来
-Hey,come here.  -Jane,no,turn around.
简 没事的 快过来
Jane,it's ok,come here.
行动
Team A and B move.
目标人物桑德斯出现
We've got a visual on Saunders.
行动
Move now.
斯蒂芬!
Stephen!
我被火力压制了
I am pinned down.
桑德斯有直升机接应
Saunders has a helicopter.
呼叫空中支援
Call in air support now.
重复 呼叫空中支援
I repeat,call in air support now.
我们需要空中支援
We need air support.
两架海军的F18
I have got a flight of 2 US Marine F18s.
已经起飞
Just off the marine.
代号守护天使
Call sign Guardian Angel.
收到
Copy that.
守护天使 守护天使 这里是看门狗
Guardian Angel,Guardian Angel,this is Watchdog.
我们遇袭 速来支援
We've got a hot on to victor bravo tango.
杰克 海军的飞机来了
Jack,the Marines are coming in.
找好掩护 重复 找好掩护
Take cover,I repeat,take cover.
直升机被击毁了
Chopper's been taken out.
-你还好吗?  -我没事
-You ok?  -Yeah.
不许动
Don't move.
还有11瓶病毒下落不明
11 vials of the virus are unaccounted for.
它们在哪?
Where are they?
没这么简单 杰克
It's not going to be that simple,Jack.
斯蒂芬 一切都结束了
Stephen,it's over.
不 还没有 杰克
No,it's not,Jack.
这只是开始
It's just the beginning.
病毒瓶在哪?
Where are the vials?
你可以对我严刑逼供进而害死几百万人
You can waste time trying to break me and kill millions of people.
或者你也可以答应我的条件
Or you can give me what I want.
我是杰克·鲍尔
This is Jack Bauer.
桑德斯已经被捕
Saunders is in custody.